{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Storm \u0026 Security Shutter Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40410/":{"taskOID":40410,"originalTaskOID":40410,"setID":703,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4972,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What are your reasons for installing security/storm shutters? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6133,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Storm/hurricane protection","answerDisplayText":"Storm/hurricane protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5539,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Security","answerDisplayText":"Security","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6188,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sun control","answerDisplayText":"Sun control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2215,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Energy conservation","answerDisplayText":"Energy conservation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4915,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Privacy","answerDisplayText":"Privacy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":888,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Attractive exterior","answerDisplayText":"Attractive exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4976,"questionDisplayText":"Floor in house of installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"On what floors will the security shutter be installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2478,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"First","answerDisplayText":"First","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5526,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Second","answerDisplayText":"Second","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6327,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Third","answerDisplayText":"Third","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3012,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Higher than three floors","answerDisplayText":"Higher than three floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4972,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What are your reasons for installing security/storm shutters? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6133,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Storm/hurricane protection","answerDisplayText":"Storm/hurricane protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5539,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Security","answerDisplayText":"Security","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6188,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sun control","answerDisplayText":"Sun control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2215,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Energy conservation","answerDisplayText":"Energy conservation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4915,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Privacy","answerDisplayText":"Privacy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":888,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Attractive exterior","answerDisplayText":"Attractive exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6133,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Storm/hurricane protection","answerDisplayText":"Storm/hurricane protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5539,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Security","answerDisplayText":"Security","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6188,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sun control","answerDisplayText":"Sun control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2215,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Energy conservation","answerDisplayText":"Energy conservation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4915,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Privacy","answerDisplayText":"Privacy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":888,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Attractive exterior","answerDisplayText":"Attractive exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4976,"questionDisplayText":"Floor in house of installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"On what floors will the security shutter be installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2478,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"First","answerDisplayText":"First","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5526,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Second","answerDisplayText":"Second","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6327,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Third","answerDisplayText":"Third","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3012,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Higher than three floors","answerDisplayText":"Higher than three floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2478,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"First","answerDisplayText":"First","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5526,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Second","answerDisplayText":"Second","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6327,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Third","answerDisplayText":"Third","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3012,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Higher than three floors","answerDisplayText":"Higher than three floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"__cache./api/resource/task/40410/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40410,"taskName":"Security or Storm Shutters - Install","taskDescription":"Install Security or Storm Shutters","xmTaskDescriptor":"Storm \u0026 Security Shutter Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":4914,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Security system Storm Shutters burglar","textMessagingName":"Storm Shutter","rolloverLongDesc":"These come in many forms, but are nearly always made of metal \u0026 can either be removed, rolled up, pivoted, slid or folded out of the way when not in use. The three most common types are storefront shutters used in urban areas, hurricane shutters in storm-prone areas \u0026 entranceway gates for mansions.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes riot, hurricane, \u0026 entrance gates or shutters.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Security or Storm Shutters.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Storm \u0026 Security Shutter Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace Storm Shutters","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":67,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Security or Storm Shutters Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Security or Storm Shutters - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Security or Storm Shutter Project","urlName":"Security-or-Storm-Shutters-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Storm Shutter Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Security Shutters Installation","searchKeywords":"Security,system,Storm,Shutters,burglar,protection,surveillance,sercuirty,secure,safe,protective,protect,windows,alarms","emcCategoryOid":-12043,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":703,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564373324358pwspr009F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}